(As of this moment,)
(you can share everything about yourselves.)
(Their age and job are finally revealed.)
(As unexpected twists unfold,)
(the residents' decisions take a turn.)
(Just how interested is she in me?)
(Kim Seon Ho does not have a date tomorrow.)
(Are you going out on a date?)
(No comment.)
(A split-second decision creates a rift between them.)
(I've been wanting to talk to you.)
(Unexpressed feelings toward Seon Ho reach him.)
(Honestly, I kept thinking about Seon Ho.)
(Where do they stand amid the missed connections?)
(Love Against Time)
You can drop the honorifics, Seon Ho.
Sure.
You said the other day that you had a sore throat.
I brought warm water just in case.
- Really?
- Yes. Let me know if you need it.
- You said it was pretty bad.
- What?
- Seriously? You're so thoughtful.
- what?
Na Young told me earlier that...
it sounded like my voice was breaking.
No. You sound the same.
- Really? Actually, - Yes.
my voice usually sounds prettier and more pleasant than this.
(Smiling)
- Isn't the weather great?
- It is.
(Going out for the first time with someone she was interested in)
We never engaged in a conversation in the House.
I already had my 1st and 2nd choices in mind.
I always wanted to talk to you because you were my second choice.
Really?
But did you want to talk to me?
- Yes.
- Really?
You were also the second person I was curious about.
- Yes.
- Take the water out and drink it.
- I had no idea.
- Oh, this? Is this it?
- Yes.
- Why is it so big?
- There's a lid here.
- I see. There's a lid.
I looked for an insulated bottle. And that was the only one.
- The temperature is perfect.
- Is it perfect?
Gosh, this is nice.
That's good.
I didn't know.
I wanted to talk to you, so I said things like...
"Where are you going, Seon Ho?" I asked you that several times.
- Yes, you did.
- Right? I did.
And I just did a little bow.
I said things like, "There." And I left.
- But it didn't show...
- Yes?
at all.
The thing is, I only smile at the people I'm interested in.
But you smile at everyone.
So I couldn't tell.
When I'm flustered, I can't help but smile.
- Really?
- Especially when I'm nervous.
You have the prettiest smile. Did you know that?
You have the most beautiful smile.
Really? Thank you. Gosh.
- My goodness.
- Oh, my.
(Lee Se Young)
- I'm curious about these two.
- Yes, me too.
I actually think they might hit it off.
This is a good chance for Seon Ho to get to know Ro Bin.
- He can get to know her better now.
- Yes. He can totally do that.
- I agree.
- A party for the unchosen ones.
(The party for the unchosen ones takes place in the House.)
- I bet they're happy this happened.
- This actually worked out for them.
- It ended up helping them instead.
- Yes.
That's why this is making me nervous.
I think they're going to hit it off.
- You think they'll hit it off?
- Is that so, Ye Ji?
- I'm worried about Ye Ji.
- You think so, Ye Ji?
Wait, she's not Ye Ji.
- Wait. What was that about?
- I'm sorry.
(Ye Na is feeling for Ye Ji every week.)
You know, Ye Ji...
chose Do Gon out of spite...
in the heat of the moment.
- Right.
- Then they got to go on a date.
- But...
- So they went on a date.
While she was on a date with Do Gon,
her head was filled with thoughts...
- about Seon Ho.
- She only thought about him.
- She felt bad for him.
- She felt bad.
- Right.
- This is driving me crazy.
Then did you get a chance to talk to everyone?
No. I...
With only one person?
I've only talked to one lady I went on a date with.
- Really?
- Yes.
- I see.
Are you an expressive type when you're in a relationship?
Yes, when I'm in a relationship.
- You're expressive?
- Totally.
I don't have to hide my feelings when I'm in a relationship.
(They're sharing a conversation for the first time.)
You're a great driver.
(The two of them arrive near the bakery.)
Do you know where the cafe is? I mean, the bakery?
- Wait. It's...
- Okay.
Wait.
(Looking around)
Hold on, Seon Ho.
I can't see.
Hold on a second.
Thank you.
(Covering)
What's this?
(Heart-pounding)
Gosh, hold on.
He's covering her head.
- This.
- Yes.
You know what?
I think we're all very much charmed by Seon Ho.
We usually let these gestures go without making a comment.
- Right.
- But we're pointing out...
everything he does.
- It's like when he's breathing, - Everything he does.
we'd be like, "Why are you breathing like that?"
(Obsessing over Seon Ho's action)
- "Why drink water like that?" - We're giving it meaning.
- We're doing that to everything.
- Yes.
- I think we should calm down first.
- Right.
- That's right.
- Right?
- I'm sorry.
- We should calm down.
- Let's stop doing that.
- We forgot to do our job.
(Pondering)
Why are they standing so close?
- Why is he so tall?
Why does he look taller today?
Why is he covering her so well?
(We're watching.)
What's this?
I see. This is the bakery.
- Is that the one?
- Yes.
I don't think it is.
That's not it.
Wait, Seon Ho.
Where are we now?
(Getting close)
Let's go this way.
We have to take the long way around.
Okay.
(Seon Ho locates the bakery.)
- Is this the place?
- Yes.
Do you want to buy the bread and head back right away?
That sounds good too.
Let's do that then. We can just buy some bread.
Do you like bread?
- Me?
- Yes.
I enjoy eating it when it's available.
You do?
- Then...
- What kind of bread do you like?
I'm not picky. I like everything.
First, let's get some morning rolls.
- Okay.
- And...
- let's get one of these.
- This looks good.
- Right?
- Yes.
- Olives? This looks good.
- What's this?
- Do you want to try this?
- Yes.
- Great.
- This should be enough.
- That...
- I'll carry that.
What's this?
- This looks good too.
- Let's get that too.
This too.
Are we buying too much?
Is this enough? There are eight of us.
- This should be more than enough.
- You think so?
Some people might not eat it.
- Guessing their portion is hard.
- Right.
Thank you.
- Thank you. Bye.
- Bye.
(How will their day in the House go?)
- This is going to taste so good.
- It's a lot of food.
(Meanwhile, Ryun Gi and Min Young are going on a date.)
- I...
- Are you feeling okay?
- Am I feeling okay?
- Yes.
I'm full of energy right now...
- Really? Then...
- because the meds...
- have worn off a lot.
- Really?
- Right. You were on chemo. Right?
- Yes.
The chemo side effects are pretty rough.
Right.
How many more rounds do you have left?
I have to get eight rounds.
- I'm on the fourth one now.
- That's good.
- I'm halfway there.
- Yes.
What's important is that I keep losing weight.
It feels like my energy is weakening.
- That's the hard part.
- You know what?
I also lost about 27kg or 28kg.
I didn't realize it back then.
But my legs were so bony like chopsticks.
I lost weight to the point of looking sick.
Right.
But I gained the weight back once it was over.
So it will come back.
- Thank you...
- Sure.
for saying that.
I don't know yet.
That's why when people get sick,
they talk less and act more carefully...
around other people.
I think because of that, people can't see your charms.
You can date anyone you want...
if you can be yourself like this.
- I can date anyone I want?
- Yes. I mean it.
This is when your self-esteem is low.
- Right.
- When she doesn't like you back,
you'd think, "I knew it. It's because I'm sick."
"I'm not enough for her." You start blaming yourself.
- Right.
- But...
looking back, you have to think like you're a prince.
When she doesn't like you back,
- you should go, "Oh, no." - What?
"She doesn't like me."
- "It's her loss." - "How dare she..."
- "not like me back?" - Right.
"Poor thing. It's her loss."
That's what you should think.
So don't put too much pressure on yourself.
Just go for it.
Having a friend like Min Young...
- would be so reliable.
- Exactly.
She'd boost your self-esteem.
It's not just a regular date. Looking at how it's going,
they're talking about their illness...
and she's trying to boost his self-esteem.
- This is nice.
- Right.
- It's a helpful date too.
- I agree.
That's why...
when we were preparing dinner last night,
I decided to keep an open mind...
and try to talk to more people.
- Right.
- That's what I thought.
Yesterday was just the beginning for me.
- Everything is...
- That's good.
starting now.
You're amazing.
(They arrive at the first spot.)
- Let's park it here.
- Yes.
We're going to the Han River today.
Really? No way.
- The weather is amazing.
- Yes.
We're going to the Han River.
We're going to pick up the picnic set here.
You're so thoughtful.
(Thoughtful Ryun Gi planned a Han River date.)
- Is this the place?
- Yes.
- What a cute puppy. Hello.
- Hi.
Hi.
- You're not afraid of dogs.
- I have a dog.
What?
- They're super friendly.
- My goodness.
(Min Young, the dog owner, pats the dog like a pro.)
Aren't you a cute puppy?
Min Young, you can pick the toast.
- I'll pick the sandwich.
- Yes.
- Kaya ham cheese toast.
- We'll take the bulgogi sandwich.
- Bulgogi sandwich.
- That's all.
- Yes.
No.
(Min Young quickly pays for the food.)
You get the next one.
This isn't good.
I can't let you pay.
- I'm cool like that.
- Thank you.
You...
- I'll prepare the drinks too.
- Thank you.
How beautiful.
It's acting like a baby.
Right. The dog suddenly came into my arms.
It really looks like a baby. Like a human baby.
I'm doing my own research now.
What research?
I want to know how I can make good use of...
- this camera.
- Look.
(He naturally takes pictures of Min Young.)
That one came out nicely.
(A cute girl with a cute puppy)
It's cute because it's big.
(Glancing over)
When I first met you,
I didn't expect this kind of vibe from you.
- Me? Really?
- Yes.
Why is that?
When we first met, I noticed that you were very shy.
Yes.
I haven't been on a lot of dates with guys.
- You haven't had many boyfriends?
- So...
- I haven't had a lot of boyfriends.
- Okay.
I don't like doing things with people...
I don't feel comfortable around.
And it shows.
But...
after talking to you quite a bit,
I thought it'd be fun to go out with you.
I wanted to talk to you a bit more too.
- Thank you.
- So I chose you.
Then we got to go on a date.
Did it make you feel good?
Yes. I was like, "Does he feel the same way?"
That's good.
(Gazing)
Actually,
- when...
- Yes?
I was crying in the kitchen, you came over.
- The things you told me...
- Yes?
- made you sound very experienced.
- Really?
(Day One)
(Ryun Gi was crying alone after reading his journal.)
What is it?
(Min Young approached Ryun Gi.)
- Who made you cry?
- No.
Don't cry.
Everyone is so amazing.
You're amazing too.
You should be proud of it.
You can brag about it to people.
I mean it.
(Her kind words comforted him.)
- Gosh.
- I see.
I might fall in love with her.
Me too. I would be so grateful.
- Right.
- Exactly. I mean, he cried.
- He showed her the real him.
- Yes.
You rarely get to see this real side...
- of anyone. You know?
- Right.
- You rarely show it to people.
On top of that, she comforted him.
If I were him, I would be impressed by her.
- She embraced his pain.
- She did.
- I'd fall in love then. Yes.
- He might rely on her too.
You sounded nonchalant when you told me those things.
But to me,
you sounded experienced.
- But... Really?
- And I was grateful for that.
I wanted to tell you about how I felt if there was a time for it.
Actually, I always ended up in a relationship...
with someone comfortable...
- like you.
- Really?
I only dated people I've known for a long time.
I see.
There were times...
when friendships turned into romantic relationships.
Of course, other couples might get more butterflies...
in the beginning of their relationship.
I want someone...
whom I can feel comfortable with even if we're not doing...
anything special.
You seemed comfortable in the House.
So I wondered if you weren't interested in anyone.
That crossed my mind.
Should I be more serious then?
(Smiling)
(The two of them are growing closer...)
(balancing between comfort and excitement.)
Let's go.
This is a therapeutic date.
(Hangang Park)
(A fresh spring breeze is blowing over Hangang Park.)
- This place is beautiful.
- Yes.
- The weather is great.
- Which way should we go?
Over there.
What a great spot.
(Their Han River date is off to a great start.)
Gosh, it's beautiful indeed.
(The two of them set up in a breezy area.)
It's so beautiful. Wait.
(Staring)
- Why? You look great today.
- What?
I'm wearing a lot of makeup today.
- Shall we?
- Thank you.
Should I kneel down here?
(Bursting into laughter)
(Ryun Gi makes Min Young laugh.)
You're so funny that you're making me drool.
- How do you feel? Hungry yet?
- Yes.
A dessert sounds perfect now.
Nice.
Actually, that's why...
Once you see this, you're going to be so surprised.
Show me.
What is it? Show me.
Like this?
- Ta-da.
- That's great.
You're so sweet.
- What do you think? Is it touching?
- This is so touching. Yes.
It's so touching. You brought my favorite dessert.
Let's eat little by little. Take your time.
Okay.
(Munching on the snack)
- You really like those crackers.
- Yes.
I can't seem to forget that.
Thank you so much.
How beautiful.
What a relaxing day.
Yes. You can relax today.
It was fun to find out everyone's age and job yesterday.
Right. Seriously.
Whose information shocked you the most?
- You.
- Me?
- Really?
- Yes.
You were nothing like I imagined.
I don't look like a researcher, right?
No.
I didn't know you were that smart.
You're like one of those guys I'd see at church.
It was an unexpected charm.
You didn't know I was that smart?
I don't know much about researchers.
But I thought they had to be incredibly smart to be one.
I was like, "He's that smart?"
- Do you need an armored vehicle?
- Yes, totally.
Tell me how you make one of those.
(Finding her adorable)
I think some dust got in my eye because of the breeze.
Do you need to get rid of it? Do you need help?
- I think I got it out.
- No, you didn't.
(Getting closer)
It's still in your eye.
(Worried)
My glitter.
Don't look!
Why are you looking at me?
- I don't know.
- It's going in.
- It didn't come out.
- Don't look.
- I know.
- Seriously.
- This looks like a relationship...
- between two comfortable friends.
- Right.
They're so cute together.
When girls tell you not to look, you shouldn't.
- We really can't?
- You can't.
- Really?
- We can't tease you more.
- We really shouldn't look?
- You really shouldn't.
We don't want you to look.
- For real?
- Yes.
At first, we'll be gentle and say, "Oh, don't look."
But after a couple of times, we'd go,
"I told you to stop."
"Why are you doing that?"
- Things will get awkward then.
- Yes.
Then we won't say anything the whole day.
Why? You don't like that?
This is a fun date.
You're so funny.
I'm comfortable and having a lot of fun.
- Really?
- Yes.
- That's a good thing, right?
- It's great.
You're probably the only one I feel this comfortable around.
I feel like I've been chosen.
Yes. That's exactly it.
Min Young took the lead in making me feel comfortable.
So the mood between us relaxed.
And I could be myself around her.
I could feel...
different things when I spent time with her.
So she kept surprising me.
(How will they remember their date today?)
What... Wait. The breeze...
It's a bit windy, right?
Do you want to play games?
Games? Sounds good.
I do want to play Halli Galli. It's been a while.
Let's play it then.
- This...
- Gosh, it's been so long.
I forgot how to play this game.
(Halli Galli)
- Are they playing games?
- That's...
But you end up touching each other's hands.
- Right.
- Halli Galli.
If you like that person, it's about touching hands.
- Right.
- But if you don't like that person,
- it's just a game.
- Yes.
If you're interested in someone, that game is the perfect chance.
And it's Halli Galli of all games.
They should've played Jenga.
You show the card like this, right?
Yes. Right. And I have to...
- show it like this.
- Wait.
You startled me.
- My gosh. Let's do it again.
- Okay.
(Scrunching up)
Wait.
Oh, no. Look at them.
Their hands touched on the bell.
Wait. He just scrunched up his nose.
- Yes.
- And their hands touched too.
"Why are you breathing like that?"
"Why did you cover your mouth just now?"
"Why is your smile so beautiful?"
He totally brought this upon himself. This is...
Guys, stop playing the game.
Do you go first?
- I think so.
- Okay. I got it.
Gosh, this isn't easy.
- Are you angry?
- No.
(Flinching)
(Nervous)
I'm scared.
You...
(She makes a mistake.)
- Are you a competitive type?
- This is so annoying.
- What?
- Are you a competitive type?
- How did you know?
- I'm one of them too.
- I can tell. Yes.
- Really?
- Yes.
Aren't I really bad at this...
when I can be so competitive?
(Meanwhile, Jong Eun comes back after a hospital appointment.)
(He brings back a bag of prescribed medicine.)
- Hey. Hello.
- Hi.
How was the doctor's appointment?
- Right. It was today.
- You look very tired.
Right.
I was there since morning.
What were you up to?
- Oh, us? We went to buy bread.
- We had bread and milk.
Do you want some bread?
- Yes. We got a lot of good bread.
- What bread?
- I see.
- Yes. We bought bread.
- Did you two go?
- Yes.
- I see.
- It's just us in the House.
Yes. It's just us in the House.
- Really?
- Yes.
So we were...
- We didn't know what to do.
- We were like, "What should we do?"
- I asked him if he wanted to go.
- Yes. We bought bread.
You look so tired.
- No. I'm good.
- I...
I also get tired after visiting the hospital.
Well, I'm good.
- I'll go and wash up.
- Okay.
(Jong Eun looks more exhausted than usual.)
(Worried)
Well, the thing is, I was still...
interested in Seon Ho.
I was quite curious about him...
when we first started talking.
How should I put it?
After seeing Jong Eun,
it was like getting shot with an arrow in the heart.
I did feel guilty for some reason.
I think it was because...
I kept having feelings for Jong Eun.
So it was uncomfortable when it was the three of us.
Right.
My goodness. I guess...
Ro Bin really likes Jong Eun.
She can't give him the wrong idea.
- She can't give him the wrong idea.
- Right.
Of course, it bothers Ro Bin.
(Seon Ho comes to see Jong Eun.)
(Smiling)
Why do you keep looking at me like that?
Did you have fun?
We just bought bread and came back. That was it.
Did you guys talk a lot?
- We did.
- How was it?
Why? Are you jealous?
- What? No.
- Are you jealous?
No. I was just curious.
Then you, Ro Bin, and I... The three of us...
- didn't go out on a date?
- Yes.
Should we prepare dinner together?
Sounds good.
I feel lonely.
Or...
she's there.
We've been on a date before.
I don't like her that way.
- You don't?
- No.
My gosh, wait.
(Disappointed)
Oh, no.
Gosh, poor Ro Bin.
I see.
This is awful.
I've gone on a date with Ro Bin...
- and Min Young.
- Yes.
Even though Min Young and I didn't talk much,
I still had more fun with her.
Right. That could happen. Yes.
So I don't know.
Gosh, this is hard.
How was it for you? You guys talked.
- Ro Bin?
- Yes.
You wanted to talk to her too.
Yes.
I think that was enough.
- I mean it.
- What do you mean?
We talked enough.
I was like, "I see."
But I had more fun with Ye Ji.
(Surprised)
That was sudden!
- What? Hold on. Play that again.
- Wait.
- I'm sorry.
- What is this? It was so random.
- Go back ten seconds.
That was a definite answer, wasn't it?
- Right.
- Yes.
But I had more fun with Ye Ji.
- Now...
- See? This is it.
Seon Ho wanted to talk to...
- everyone first.
- I see.
Then it became clear to him that he was...
- most interested in her.
- Yes.
- No. He's not there yet.
- But just now...
- He just had more fun with her.
- It was more fun.
He had more fun with Ye Ji.
That's all. He just had more fun.
It's not, "I like her more."
So he might have to get to know other people more.
- I see. He has to...
- Or...
- get to know other people more?
- That's right.
I'm saying that's a possibility too.
Now that he's gotten to know these two ladies,
he might want to get to know other ladies more.
- Right.
- He might have meant that too.
- Did I lower my guard for a second?
- It's...
- It's too soon to tell.
- Right?
Right? I lowered my guard again.
(It's hard to figure out where the guys stand for now.)
I see.
I just found out that there were flip-flops here.
- I just found out too.
- Really?
I see. You came here after seeing me come out.
Yes.
We might be able to see everyone coming home from here.
You're right. They'll come up this way.
We can sit here all day, Seon Ho.
- "I see." - "Hey, you're home."
It's cool here.
It's much cooler here.
(Jong Eun comes out to the balcony.)
(Spotting them)
- What are you doing?
- Come on down.
Come down here.
I'll look around over there and go down.
Where?
(Staring)
He's standing there like the main character of a drama.
(Ro Bin can't take her eyes off Jong Eun.)
(Beckoning over)
(Jong Eun misses Ro Bin beckoning him over.)
Jong Eun. Come on down.
Okay.
- Are you not having bread?
- What?
Shall we go upstairs now?
Go upstairs now?
We're joking.
What should we make for dinner tonight?
Fried rice and pork belly.
I'm thinking about making one of those.
Right now?
Have you eaten?
- Yes.
- You didn't have lunch.
- Lunch...
- Yes.
I had lunch.
What did you have for lunch?
- Lunch?
- We had some bread.
Bread.
- Do you want some bread?
- That would be nice.
- Shall we go and eat that?
- Okay.
While eating bread, I'll...
- It's already 6pm.
- I know.
That's right. It's an awkward time.
Can you eat dinner after having some bread?
Right.
Pork belly?
- Let's have pork belly.
- Yes.
Yes.
(While they decide to prepare dinner)
You've arrived at your destination.
If you get used to it...
(Ye Ji and Do Gon are back from their date)
It's the House.
Thank you.
- I'll get changed.
- Okay.
(Pausing)
(Staring)
She's looking for him.
She'd have been so curious.
Right.
She thought about Seon Ho throughout her date.
She'd be curious to know what he's doing.
I think I went around looking for Seon Ho...
as soon as I arrived.
I wanted to talk to him. I wanted to ask him...
about what happened at the House today...
and how he spent his time.
I was curious to know how his day was.
(Glancing)
(She's curious to know about Seon Ho's day.)
(The three people are still together.)
It's really funny.
- Hey, Do Gon.
- Hey.
When did you get back?
- Is someone here?
Where are they?
- Wait.
Did you have dinner today?
I had something simple.
I wanted to eat here.
We're going to have some pork belly.
- Pork belly?
- Yes.
(Glancing)
(Waving)
(They exchanged a quick hand wave.)
He should just take care of her if he likes her.
- Even a word.
- Just one word.
- "You're back." - "You're back."
Just those words.
- He's still inexperienced.
- No.
I think he may be acting that way...
because he feels weird.
Is he a little upset?
He's not upset...
He's he acting like he's upset?
He's good at pretending...
it doesn't bother him.
That's right.
That's when I knew...
that Ye Ji went out on a date with Do Gon.
I felt...
a little weird.
"What's going on?"
Yesterday, she went on a date with me, but today, with another...
It was weird.
I had mixed feelings.
I met Seon Ho.
My head hurt from all the thoughts...
when I tried to talk to him.
(Peeping)
- What are you doing?
- We're going to play a game.
This...
- Do you want to play with us?
- Yes.
I'll get changed then.
Do you know how to play this?
(A moment later)
(The four people decide to play a game.)
Shall we decide on the penalty?
What penalty should we get?
Truth or Dare?
(This is interesting.)
- They're going to play a game.
- Truth or Dare?
That's good for Ye Ji.
- Yes.
- She'll get to know the truth.
That's right.
(Focusing)
(Truth or Dare will reveal how everyone really feels.)
When it falls,
someone will ask you a question, and you'll say the truth.
You have to be honest.
(Getting nervous)
Okay.
Are you all fine with that?
- Okay.
- No lying. Be honest.
Okay.
(The truth game begins with a strange sense of tension.)
Rock-paper-scissors.
- Rock-paper-scissors.
- Yes.
- I'm last.
Isn't going first a disadvantage?
(Jong Eun will start.)
(Pulling)
(He smoothly succeeds.)
(Second up is Do Gon.)
(Shaking)
Hold on.
Already?
(Hitting trouble from the start)
I think it's already over.
- Let's think of a question.
- Okay.
(Shaking)
(Do Gon's tower is falling.)
This is already happening on the second turn?
This is so funny.
I'm so bad at this game.
(Do Gon gets the penalty for the first round.)
What should we ask him?
(He's devastated.)
Okay. Ask away.
(Feeling nervous)
(There's a sudden silence.)
(Glancing)
Did you find someone you like?
(She's flustered.)
(Glancing)
There's someone...
I'm interested in right now.
(Nodding)
Right.
(They move right into Round 2.)
Wait.
- Already?
- That happens.
It's your turn now.
Wait.
(Shaking)
What?
No way.
He's trembling.
It's falling.
It fell!
Okay!
- That's right!
- It fell!
This is what I'm talking about.
Don't say, "No comment."
Who'll be asking?
Will they take turns asking?
- Ye Ji will be dying to know.
- Just ask away.
It's your turn.
- This is fair.
- Right.
Nice.
Let's ask him.
What should we ask him?
(Feeling anxious)
I'll ask first.
Okay.
Tell us which date...
you've enjoyed the most so far.
That's a meaningful question.
- That was a good question.
- That was good.
- Ye Ji likes it.
- Well done.
Nice.
I hope he tells them honestly.
- It's okay, right?
- It's good.
- You're good at asking questions.
- Nice.
This is what makes the game fun.
It's so difficult.
You enjoyed the date...
in the morning or afternoon of a certain day.
That's how you should say it.
Can I take some time to think about it?
You seem very nervous.
(She's curious.)
I think I liked yesterday's date.
(Seon Ho went on two dates yesterday.)
(His first date was with Min Young.)
(His second date was with Ye Ji.)
One of those two?
- Seriously...
- He is...
not saying who it is.
Who answers it like that?
Hold on. Why does he always...
leave a 50 percent chance?
(Which date left an impression on Seon Ho?)
- Rock-paper-scissors!
Rock-paper-scissors.
- Why am I always last?
Wait.
- Hold on.
- You got the wrong one.
- Can I use this hand to do this?
- Sure.
(Tapping)
- It's somewhat...
- Wait...
This is driving me crazy.
(Pushing)
It's going to fall.
Seriously.
(Smiling)
This part is just shaking.
This part seems out.
(Staring)
Please.
- You're almost there.
- The corner part is stuck.
(Sharp eyes)
(With a twisting skill)
Hold on.
Yes.
(She fails.)
You were so close.
What a shame.
You're good.
I was so close.
- Let's put these on top.
- Yes.
(It's time to ask Ye Ji.)
How many people are you interested in?
How many people?
(Thinking)
Two.
I'll ask.
The two people you're interested in...
are here.
- Are they here or not?
- Here?
That's a strong one.
This makes it fun, doesn't it?
It's strong.
But what's the definition of being interested in someone?
- Someone you're drawn to.
- Okay.
They're here.
Okay.
(Glancing)
(It's Seon Ho's turn to ask.)
Did you enjoy today's date?
- Today's date?
- Yes.
(Seon Ho asked if she enjoyed the date with Do Gon.)
- Are you asking if I enjoyed it?
- Yes.
(Nodding)
All right.
(Exclaiming)
- What?
- That's just about this.
The answer isn't important for that question.
He was expressing himself.
- Really?
- He meant, "I'm bothered by it."
That's right.
- Of course she'll say it was fun.
- Right.
That question itself...
sounds like, "Did you enjoy today's date?"
- "It's bothering me." - That's the nuance of it.
"Did you enjoy today's date?"
- I get it.
- He was expressing that in a way.
Right.
Ye Ji was asked if there was someone there...
that she was interested in.
She said yes...
and that there were two people.
I thought that would be Do Gon and me.
Do Gon is older than me.
He's a stable person,
and he's cool.
So...
I became conscious of that.
(He started becoming conscious of another man.)
After revealing our jobs yesterday,
Yes.
I wanted to take a picture...
with our great actress.
I heard there's...
a photo booth where you can take four-cut photos.
That would be nice.
I rarely take selfies.
- What is this place?
- It's a photo booth.
(Ryun Gi wanted to take pictures with Na Young.)
This is amazing.
It's so vintage and nice here.
Come to the left side.
Don't you need to check yourself in the mirror?
You have to check now.
- Why?
- They won't give you time.
- I don't need to.
- What's with that confidence?
You have such a small face.
- My face will look so big.
- Should I stand in front?
Where should I look at?
It's going to look pretty.
Let's smile.
(The excitement of their first date was captured in the photos.)
- That's nice.
- They look nice.
- That's amazing.
- What's that place?
- Where is that place?
(Exchanging looks)
Shall we go there?
- Shall we take pictures there?
- Do you want to go out on a date?
We'll be doing this.
(Yong Hwa and DK are matched for a date.)
This is so cute.
- Do you like it?
- Yes.
You know,
when I look at you,
you really have a small face.
But I also had a small face.
It's really small.
- What are you talking about?
- That's a relief.
You said you were going to stand in front,
but you leaned to the wall.
I was worried because your actions...
and words didn't match.
- Did you feel betrayed?
- Yes.
You're the one with a small face,
and you keep telling me that I have a small face.
Yours is really small.
(After a walk with some easy conversation,)
(they arrive at the date spot chosen by Ryun Gi.)
What is this place?
I heard the owner takes these photos...
and turns them into postcards to sell here.
That's amazing.
They're so pretty.
(They decided to write postcards to each other.)
This one?
I really like this one.
(Na Young chose one right away.)
(Ryun Gi takes his time to choose a postcard.)
I'll start writing first.
- Did you pick one?
- Yes.
I like the mood here.
The mood of these two people.
The mood?
- They seem so comfortable.
- Yes. It's so beautiful.
What are you going to write about?
What should I write about?
Your first impression...
- And how I feel today?
- How they're different.
Okay.
Don't look.
(They start writing postcards...)
(while reminiscing about their first meeting.)
(How have their first impressions of each other...)
(changed since then?)
I'm done.
Shall we exchange them?
Right now? I feel shy.
Why? When else will we read them?
I want to read it now.
(They exchange the postcards they wrote for each other.)
This is how you wrote it.
- Can I read it out loud?
- What?
No.
Can't I read it out loud?
Okay.
I happened to be the last person to walk in.
I thought, "I should walk in confidently."
"I met Ryun Gi for the first time when I greeted everyone."
"He's not really my type."
"He's someone who knows how to empathize with other people..."
"and take something away from them. He's a pure and humble person."
"He's an honest person who laughed and cried, and found his own way..."
"even through the difficult process."
I'm truly honored to have gotten to know you like this.
(I'm truly honored, Kim Ryun Gi.)
Thank you. You said such nice things.
This is really embarrassing.
- You're not crying, right?
- I almost cried.
When I first met Na Young,
I saw her as a bright and cheerful girl...
who brings positive energy to the people around her.
Sometimes, when she opens up and shares her honest...
and sincere thoughts,
I find her really charming.
You got that right.
I think her experiences and her thoughtful side...
are truly admirable,
so I hope more people get to see this side of her.
Smiley face.
Thank you.
What is it?
(Have they changed since they first met?)
So this is how it feels. We shouldn't have read that.
Why?
(Min Young is back from the date.)
What?
I'm...
- I'm not feeling so well...
- Are you feeling sick?
I think I'm losing my voice.
- It's starting to go.
- Or...
Right?
Drink some ginger latte.
There's a ginger latte?
I'll make it for you.
It's good.
- Really?
- I love ginger latte.
Big sis will make you a cup of ginger latte!
(Big sis is off.)
Hi.
(Just then, she runs into Do Gon.)
- You see, it seems like...
- Yes?
Ro Bin's cold got worse.
All of a sudden?
Did she already have a bit of a cold?
- I'm not sure.
- Ro Bin might've said...
she had a sore throat.
But she looks quite sick right now.
Oh, dear.
I was going to make ginger latte, but we don't have ginger tea.
There's no lemon marmalade either.
(Worried)
We don't have any, do we?
I've asked for it.
- We don't have ginger tea.
- Fever...
- Is that so?
- Do you drink citrus tea?
I do, and I like citrus tea.
- Do you drink citrus chamomile tea?
- She already made one.
Yes, of course.
- It's citrus chamomile tea.
- Thank you.
Drink it even if it's bad.
No, I'll drink it. I'll definitely drink it all.
- Do you have a fever?
- What?
No, I don't think so.
- Should I take my temperature?
- You're like a doctor.
- Really?
- I brought one.
What's this? How do you use it?
Get ready.
Your voice sounds a little weird.
Yes, I've kind of lost it.
- Fever...
- You don't have a fever.
Right? I don't feel like I do.
(Do Gon takes Ro Bin's temperature himself.)
No, you don't have a fever.
I did go to the hospital and get some medicine.
- Today?
- I was told not to talk much,
but I talked a lot.
- So you shouldn't talk much.
- No.
It's okay to talk in a small voice.
Get some rest while you drink that.
Okay, thank you.
(Teasing)
(Feeling shy)
I told him on purpose.
Ro Bin is sick.
Well done.
I...
I guess I kind of enjoy this. Oh, dear.
(Cupid Min Young works her magic.)
It was fun.
(1 hour later)
(Do Gon returns with something he bought outside.)
Wait.
Yes?
Yes? What is it?
Do you feel better?
- No, I'm still...
- Here's some medicinal herb tea.
Thank you.
Jujube medicinal herb tea.
- Drink one right now.
- Okay.
The rest... You can just leave these here.
What's this?
- Ginger tea.
- You need hot water for this.
- Right.
- I'll leave this downstairs.
- This...
- Are you taking this downstairs?
- It's warm. Yes.
- I...
- No, I'll do it.
Thank you.
I'd better drink it.
- Right now?
- Right now.
It's warm. I appreciate it.
- Being sick is a no-no.
- Exactly.
- As expected.
- Did you see that?
- I knew he'd do that.
- Gosh, Do Gon.
Today's ginger tea timing was nice.
- It was very nice.
- Yes, very nice.
- Very nice - Nice
- He's always so cool.
- Do Gon is the best.
I feel at ease when Do Gon appears.
- Right?
- I feel at ease.
He just hits the spot.
When someone takes care of you when you're sick,
you can't help but catch feelings.
- Absolutely.
- How is he that sweet?
(In the bottles are Do Gon's feelings.)
(Ye Ji and Ro Bin are the only ones in the girls' room.)
Really, Ye Ji.
I've never dated before.
It's only natural for it to be tough, right?
Totally.
Was your first relationship also a little tough?
Of course. It was really tough.
I keep... You know...
I keep thinking, "Can I start a conversation?"
You know, things like that?
There's a need for us to be...
- more proactive.
- Is that so?
It's already Day Four.
Tomorrow will be Day Five.
There are only two days left.
Exactly. We're short on time.
True.
Even if we act with more enthusiasm...
It's definitely easier said than done.
Bon appetit.
- Good job.
- Thank you for the meal.
Let's dig in, or it'll get cold.
- Whose rice is this?
- Mine.
Is that so? Then I'll put mine here.
(Each takes a seat.)
After dinner...
(The 2 sit 1 seat away from each other.)
Don't we have six people?
- Hold on. 1, 2...
- Would you like this seat?
(The 2 sit 1 seat away from each other.)
- Will you be sitting there, Ye Ji?
- No.
- Would you like this seat?
- I'm feeling a bit hot.
- May I turn the AC on?
- Sure.
- Thank you.
- Seon Ho is left-handed, - Really?
- so he'll probably sit at the end.
- Is that so?
I didn't know he was left-handed.
- Is this yours?
- Yes.
(Leaving the end seat for left-handed Seon Ho)
- Someone is looking for you.
- Right?
(Seon Ho has been sitting in the same seat since the first day.)
(Last night's dinner)
- Can I really sit here?
- Yes.
- I'm left-handed.
- Is that so?
That's why I always take the end seat.
So this is what it's like.
It's pretty.
(Seon Ho's designated seat next to Ro Bin is left empty.)
Right?
Should I leave this in the center?
(Pulling)
- What?
- For real?
- What's going on?
(Pulling)
Is this all?
- What?
- What is it?
- Min Young...
- Min Young?
Can I?
She went to talk.
(Seon Ho abandoned his designated seat and sat next to Ye Ji.)
(This is what we're talking about!)
Congratulations.
(Impressed)
This is hip-hop.
He killed it.
Thank you.
- Thank you very much.
- Goodness, Seon Ho!
He has us twisted around his finger.
For real.
Seon Ho has changed.
For Seon Ho to have gone that far...
means he's tried hard.
- Totally.
- He put in full effort.
- After the game, - Yes?
they sort of checked...
- each other's feelings.
- Right.
It feels like Seon Ho has decided to go...
- straight for her.
- Did he?
Ye Ji's right arm...
and Seon Ho's left arm will touch.
- That's correct.
- He wants to reach her.
Yes, he wants their arms to touch.
That's insane.
- What's this?
- Is there no sauce for this?
Did you try it?
- Over here?
- The ketchup.
It was really good.
- I can't imagine it.
- The orange was...
(Enduring the discomfort, Seon Ho secured the seat next to Ye Ji's.)
Having meat after vegan food is a bit...
(Do Gon brings up the date he had with Ye Ji.)
- It didn't taste vegan at all.
- Right?
What was the name again? Orange something.
It was deep-fried something.
- I'm getting curious.
- Orange onion?
It was really good.
- I can't imagine it.
- The orange was deep-fried.
It felt like eating fried chicken.
The restaurant deep-fried oranges.
That's how it felt.
Either way, the food was good.
I was conscious of Do Gon.
I felt frustrated, as if I were being chased by something.
Be wishy-washy,
and things might just end nowhere.
(For the first time, Seon Ho has grown impatient.)
(After dinner)
(Screaming)
What's wrong?
Did you get hurt?
My nail broke. Right here.
- Does it hurt?
- Yes.
What should we do? How did it happen?
- My nail was already kind of loose.
- I see.
Give me a second.
(Seon Ho heads somewhere.)
(Looking around)
(Found the first-aid kit)
- Oh, my gosh.
- It's over here.
Here.
(Just in time, Ye Ji came for some medicine.)
Put this on, and don't use your hand.
Here, show me.
Is this where...
Should we apply it here?
(Being thorough)
I'll do it.
I'll do it. Stay still.
(Laughing)
Like so.
(Lightly)
- Is it waterproof?
- Yes, it's like rubber gloves.
(The moment when his feelings are conveyed through her fingertip)
This is tough to roll down.
I think he's done,
- but he keeps touching her.
- Right?
- He was done a long time ago.
- Totally.
You might as well put a cast on.
That's practically a cast.
Aren't we all set? We've seen it all.
We already have one couple.
- Yes, congratulations.
- For real.
Congratulations, Seon Ho and Ye Ji.
- It's certain.
- He's back.
But guys.
(You never know.)
- Don't do that.
- Stop spoiling it.
- No.
- Guys.
- Stop it.
- Don't.
- Can things get twisted here?
- Guys.
Things are going completely fine.
The two are set in stone.
- How can things go wrong?
- We're being rash.
I want to be rash.
I want to be rash too.
Don't take Love Against Time for granted.
What a golden saying.
Right? Don't take Love Against Time for granted.
Seon Ho is expressing his feelings to me.
That was what crossed my mind.
I was very grateful.
My heart also fluttered. It made me happy.
Just in case, take a few...
- Okay.
- Band-Aids.
- Thank you.
- No problem.
This much should do.
Thanks for driving.
Don't worry about it. Good job today.
Good job to you as well.
You found it yourself.
True.
(Sighing)
Do Gon, did you have a productive conversation?
I did.
The time gave me a chance to sort things out...
- Really?
- for myself.
Did it go well?
I decided to go back...
- to how I was...
- Right.
in the beginning.
And you, Jong Eun?
- I plan...
- Did you make progress?
to be like you.
You know...
There's no other way, is there?
- Leave no regrets.
- Go for it.
No looking back.
- Isn't that better?
- Yes.
(The four have come out for some fresh air in the nice weather.)
It's nice.
It sure is.
But it could suddenly become cold.
Gosh, the moon looks pretty.
(The moon is particularly bright today.)
(The moonlight softly illuminates the city at night.)
(Settling in at the end of the terrace,)
(where the moon is clearly visible)
(Jong Eun stares quietly at the moon, as if deep in thought.)
Where did Jong Eun go?
- He's at the very end.
- Over...
Is he over there alone?
He's enjoying some solitude.
The moon looks...
particularly big from over there.
- Isn't the moon pretty?
- It's pretty.
Do you want to go there?
We might be able to see it better.
- Where?
- Should we go over to that side?
Come over here.
(Ro Bin walks over to Jong Eun, using the moon as an excuse.)
Doesn't the cold air make you feel like you're about to cough?
- Jong Eun, what are you doing?
- What are you doing?
- What?
- Are you lost in thought?
No, I was enjoying the night view.
You were?
Yes.
Jong Eun, have you thought of your wish?
- Me?
- You forgot, didn't you?
Well, no.
Did you forget about it?
No, I've been thinking about it.
You forgot, right?
No, I didn't. I've really been thinking...
But you did... Really?
Have you been thinking about it?
I see.
Today was hectic,
- having to go to the hospital.
- Right?
What did the result say?
- It turned out fine.
- Did it?
What did the blood test say?
My platelet count was a little high,
but the doctor said it was still okay.
Does your mouth still feel dry?
Yes, but I think time will take care of it.
You don't know when it'll get better, do you?
- It...
- It'll last forever.
Forever?
- Yes.
- How come?
It could last forever or not.
It's a complete gamble...
since everyone is different.
I believe 100 percent that you'll get better.
- Really?
- Yes.
How come?
What?
I'm just...
Even when I'm sick,
I never think of the worst.
Why do you think it'll last forever...
- and not get better?
- What?
Why do you think it won't get better?
- I do think it'll get better.
- I see.
- But?
- But this is lifelong homework.
You worry too much, don't you?
- Me?
- Yes.
- I'm not worried.
- You're not?
- I do worry, - Yes?
- but not too deeply.
- Right.
It's just...
I just don't know what to do.
It's tough.
- Is it?
- Yes.
- Have you talked...
- Yes?
with the others a lot?
Honestly, I just...
Who have you talked with the most?
- It's probably you, Ro Bin.
- Seriously?
Like having actual conversations.
Is that so?
I see.
You know, I...
Expressing...
my feelings first...
and doing things like that are both a first for me.
- Is that so?
- Yes.
I've never done it before in my life.
So I don't know how to do it.
I'm really bad at it.
I don't even know...
- if I'm on the right track.
- Me too.
(Laughing)
I've been wanting to know what kind of talks...
- we should have.
- That's natural.
I was able to talk to many people,
and I talked to them a lot in the earlier days.
- Really?
- Yes.
What's the conclusion you came to?
There are some...
who have expressed their interest in me.
But I have someone in mind.
Among the people you're interested in?
No, not among the people.
I've settled on someone.
That's right.
You're too slow.
Hurry up and talk to others.
Spend the rest of your time investing in that one person.
But there's someone I'd like to get to know.
I see.
Right.
They can't reach each other.
- Jong Eun is super closed off.
- Right?
- This is a tough one.
- True.
But we know how he feels.
You can't do anything about it.
- For sure.
- You're right.
Aren't you cold?
- No, I'm not.
- Is that so?
I'm totally fine right now.
I want to keep this conversation going,
but do you want to as well?
- Me? With you?
- Yes.
Well...
I'm willing to talk to you...
until...
you want to.
But I have someone...
- Of course.
- I'd like to get to know.
I want you to talk to her as much as possible.
- I see.
- Yes.
I want you to have as many conversations as possible. I...
There's really not enough time.
I didn't know what to say. I was at a loss for words.
It was upsetting.
No matter what I said,
it felt like it bounced off of him.
Then...
Think about your wish and tell me.
Got it.
Think about it, okay?
(Do Gon can hear Ro Bin and Jong Eun's conversation.)
- Was he listening to them?
- Oh, no.
- For real?
- The camera angle.
- What's with the angle?
- My gosh.
Was he listening to them just now?
- Gosh.
- Seriously.
(Heartbroken)
- Do Gon is unbelievable.
- Right?
Yong Hwa.
My heart hurts.
It's really...
My heart is breaking into pieces.
I'm losing it.
It hurts.
(Do Gon forces himself to look away.)
Did you say you had a younger sister?
Yes, I did.
Are you close with her?
Are you going to stay here?
Me? Shall we go back inside?
Well...
It's already 11pm?
It's 11pm.
(Do Gon quietly leaves them alone.)
Jong Eun and Ro Bin were talking.
My staying there could've made things...
awkward for both of them.
That was why I intentionally left the area.
(As his feelings for Ro Bin deepen,)
(he becomes more thoughtful toward her.)
(Day 4, Do Gon has come to the Room of Time.)
(The Room of Time Guide)
(Today, if the total amount of time you allocate to each other...)
(reaches 110 minutes or more, you'll go on a date.)
(From this point on,)
(the total time you've allocated to each other...)
(will no longer be revealed.)
What?
So it's no longer revealed at the end of the date?
- There's no pressure.
- No.
There's no pressure.
The total amount is no longer revealed.
If so, asking her out on a date is the right thing to do.
Using up all the time on that person is much better.
Do Gon would totally think like that.
There's no pressure if the total amount is...
- kept a secret.
- Totally.
When I saw the changed rule...
Up until yesterday,
I thought asking her out...
on a date every time...
was making her feel uncomfortable.
That's why I didn't use all my time on her.
But today,
the time we allocated to each other...
won't be revealed.
"Let's follow my heart." This was the mindset I had.
The first good feeling I felt...
hasn't changed.
(Do Gon's heart couldn't be hidden.)
It's warm. Thank you.
- You can't be sick.
- Right.
(Seo Ro Bin)
I want to go on a date with her before it's too late.
I want to talk with her.
The first thing to do before talking to her...
was to create that opportunity.
(Do Gon allocates 100 minutes to Ro Bin.)
(He uses all of his heart.)
(Seo Ro Bin)
(Ro Bin will not know about Do Gon's genuine heart.)
Hundred Do Gon is back.
Do Gon is surely the secure type.
Secure Do Gon.
If Ro Bin spends ten minutes,
- the date will happen.
- Right.
- That will make it 110 minutes.
- Please!
Ro Bin was slightly pushed back by Jong Eun.
- Right.
- She was pushed back.
- Right!
She might not spend 100 minutes...
- on Jong Eun.
- Right.
I'm so curious about what she'll do.
(Ro Bin enters the Room of Time.)
Let's see.
I think I've...
checked his heart to a certain extent.
He still wants to...
learn about the others other than me.
Even still,
I thought that I should follow my heart.
(Kim Jong Eun)
(Ro Bin sends Jong Eun her time...)
(even though she knows his heart.)
(Ro Bin allocates 100 minutes to Jong Eun.)
- Come on!
- Gosh!
- Everyone's heart is the same.
- Right.
They all spent 100 minutes?
- Gosh!
- Ro Bin...
- is only thinking about Jong Eun.
- She keeps going for Jong Eun.
- Things are tough.
- Right.
- That was cold.
(Jong Eun also entered the Room of Time.)
(His time heads to one name without hesitation.)
Min Young was always...
my first priority.
I wanted to talk with her again.
That was why I spent 100 minutes on her.
(Jong Eun allocates 100 minutes to Min Young.)
If we don't find a connection even after that,
I think I'll try to turn my eyes to someone else.
(Where will Min Young's heart head toward?)
I felt torn about what to do,
but ever since the moment I came here,
Seon Ho was the only one who got my attention.
There was still some time left.
I thought I could try to approach him a little more.
"This is how close I can get to him."
I spent 50 minutes on him with that thought.
(Min Young allocates 50 minutes to Seon Ho.)
I've talked a lot with Jong Eun.
I've talked with Ryun Gi as well.
Do Gon was the only one I haven't talked with.
That was why I spent a little bit of my time on him.
(Han Do Gon)
(Min Young allocates 30 minutes to Do Gon.)
I really enjoyed...
today's date with Ryun Gi.
I thought I had a great time with him.
That was why I spent some of time on him as well.
(Min Young allocates 20 minutes to Ryun Gi.)
(Min Young's heart doesn't seem to know where to go.)
It really feels like they are...
all looking at the back of each other's heads.
It's pretty much a sports day.
(A love line that feels like a relay race)
- A relay race.
- It's a sports day here.
The baton is passed on to the next person.
- The running won't stop.
- It's endless.
- Gosh!
When will the running stop?
- Things are so hard.
- Exactly.
(The target of Ryun Gi's time)
It felt like things had just begun for me.
I thought deeply about who I had to pick.
During the date with Min Young...
and Na Young,
Ro Bin kept lingering inside of my head.
(After the date of Day 2)
Without realizing it,
I think I hurt you.
I'm sorry.
It's totally understandable.
I also worried about the same thing.
Don't feel bad about it.
(The conversation with Ro Bin kept bothering him.)
I want to spend a lot more time...
with Ro Bin.
In the Room of Time,
it felt like I had to go all in with my time.
(Ryun Gi's time starts heading toward Ro Bin again.)
(Ryun Gi allocates 100 minutes to Ro Bin.)
- What?
- Really?
See? I saw that coming.
His self-esteem...
- was brought down by Ro Bin.
- Right.
But after meeting Na Young...
- and Min Young, his self-esteem...
- Min Young.
- went back up.
- He recovered his self-esteem.
- Right.
- Now,
- he gained the courage...
- To go forward.
of being able to do well during dates again.
- Right.
That's great.
That's impressive.
(Ryun Gi meets Ro Bin after making his decision.)
When are you going to lend me your book?
Oh, right!
I was going to...
read it yesterday.
But you ran away.
Right.
Are you going to give it to me now?
I'll give it to you now.
I was reading it.
- You're lying.
- I'm serious.
You're lying!
I was reading it, but I couldn't focus.
It kept making me fall asleep.
I should spend some time reading this.
Right. It's so quiet here.
Are you busy? Do you have plans for tomorrow?
- Plans for tomorrow?
- Yes.
Why do you ask? It's a secret.
Okay, then.
I can't do anything about it if it's a secret.
No. It's not a secret.
It'll be great to spend time together if you have time.
Let's go out for a cup of tea.
Let's hang out. I was going to be bored on my own.
But why did you say it was a secret?
- Why hide it?
- I don't know.
Did you hide it because you felt shy?
Yes.
It was so quiet without you today.
- No way.
- I'm serious.
What did you do today?
Who were you with today?
- Today...
- Weren't you with Seon Ho?
I was with Seon Ho.
We talked with each other for a while.
(Smiling)
- What is it?
- What?
- It seems like you're loosening up.
- Me?
- Yes.
I feel comfortable.
- You do?
- Yes.
You look a lot different from how you looked the first day.
I feel a lot more comfortable being with you.
- That's a relief.
- A lot more comfortable.
That's great for me if you feel that way.
Seeing you feel anxious...
made me feel anxious as well.
- Really?
- Feeling anxious...
meant that you kept thinking about me.
But thinking about me in that sense...
- made me feel anxious as well.
- Right.
I couldn't expect where that would lead to.
Right.
I feel disappointed about that day...
because...
I kept freezing...
and acted awkwardly in front of you.
I wasn't able to ask you the things I wanted to ask you.
- Really?
- Yes.
Because I felt disappointed about that day,
I wanted to be able to spend more time with you.
If you have the time,
I thought we could have a cup of tea together.
- That sounds good.
- I wanted to be able...
- to spend time with you.
- I should get...
a good night's sleep, then.
Feel comfortable.
Right. I do feel comfortable.
I feel so comfortable at the thought of hanging out with you.
But don't feel to comfortable.
Okay.
Okay. I'll feel reasonably comfortable.
No. You can feel comfortable.
I like it that way.
(Ryun Gi carefully knocks at Ro Bin's heart.)
He's expressing himself so much.
This is one or the other.
They will end up liking each other...
- or become really close friends.
- Right.
- It seems like Ro Bin...
is thinking of him as a friend.
Oh, no.
I think it takes quite a bit of time...
- to know their own heart.
- Right.
We don't know what to expect...
- Anything can happen.
- after the date.
- Shall we go out for a walk?
- Sure.
Put on something warm.
Where should we go?
- Outside?
- Okay.
The first floor.
Nice.
Where are you two going?
Why has Seon Ho changed so much?
Will he make things happen?
He must get things settled now.
Right.
Our Seon Ho has changed!
Has he really changed?
Gosh, it looks nice.
(Seon Ho asked to talk first for the first time.)
Right. It does look nice.
It's my first time... No. I came here earlier.
(The two sit facing each other in the quiet garden.)
Gosh.
- Are you okay?
- Yes.
- Did you have fun today?
- Today?
It's a simple question.
- Yes.
Not as much as yesterday's date.
Did you have fun?
- Today?
- Yes.
Well, I didn't enjoy it as much.
But I tried to make the most of it.
Actually,
did you think that I didn't spend my time on you?
- Yesterday?
- Yes.
I knew that you...
spent your time on me yesterday.
- Yesterday?
- Yes.
How did you know?
Wouldn't you have spent your time on me?
But I didn't tell you that I spent my time on you.
I saw that you didn't go out for a date.
I thought that you had spent your time on me,
but things didn't work out.
- Am I right?
- Yes. You're right.
I see.
Did you want to spend time with me today?
- Today?
- Yes.
I hoped to...
if it were to be possible.
I enjoyed the time we spent during the last two dates.
I admit that I was curious about you.
I wanted to know if my heart had an interest...
or something beyond an interest.
I wasn't hiding my feelings.
I just wasn't sure...
about my feelings.
But now,
I feel like I should follow my heart.
I should move the way my heart moves.
These were the thoughts I had.
We've spent almost half of our time here.
Tomorrow...
- it will be over half of our time.
- It's our fifth day.
Do you think things will become clear...
after tomorrow's date?
Yes. I feel like things will become clear after tomorrow.
What about you, Ye Ji?
Are things clear for you?
Actually,
up until yesterday, you were the only one...
- I talked to.
- Right.
I went on a date...
with someone else today,
but I kept getting reminded about yesterday.
(Smirking)
So...
- That's so cute!
- My gosh.
(Bursting out in laughter)
It feels like we're peeking on them.
- Right.
- Right?
I don't know why I'm holding my breath.
Isn't it so nice to talk like this?
Right. It's great.
- I won't feel anxious anymore.
- Right.
A date will surely happen, right?
- It will surely happen.
- Right.
- I see.
It feels good to hear that.
I think I was able to...
learn more about my heart...
(He can't hide his smile.)
after going on...
a date with someone else.
- That was what it was like for me.
- I see.
(Smiling)
(Have their hearts become more certain after tonight?)
(Ye Ji enters the Room of Time.)
(She notices the new rule.)
(Holding tight)
I want to spend more time with Seon Ho from now on.
I strongly thought that I should spend time with him...
without leaving any regrets.
(Her time for Seon Ho continues to stack up.)
(Kim Seon Ho)
- What? There you go!
- There you go!
There you go!
Let's go for 200 minutes for the first time.
We'll get to see 200 minutes!
I think Ye Ji will spend 100 minutes on him.
(Kim Seon Ho)
(She stops after spending 80 minutes.)
(Kim Jong Eun)
(Ye Ji allocates 80 minutes to Seon Ho.)
(and 20 minutes to Jong Eun.)
Why?
Are you curious about him?
Why did she spend only 80 minutes...
after that conversation?
(Confused)
Is Ye Ji interested in Jong Eun?
- No, right?
- I don't think she is.
We've never seen Jong Eun talk with Ye Ji.
Right.
- Not even once.
- I don't know why she went for him.
I'll just watch.
I really feel lost.
Why 80 minutes?
(Curious)
(What is Ye Ji's heart behind not spending 100 minutes?)
(Seon Ho entered the Room of Time.)
The one I'm most interested in is Ye Ji.
I want to stop thinking and measuring with my heart.
I should follow my heart.
I didn't want to be hesitant, confused,
and vague with my heart.
(Thinking)
(Surprised)
- Hold on. What now?
- What now?
Don't be like that! This is driving me crazy.
Don't be like that!
He shouldn't have been careless until the end.
He imagined things on his own again.
"Things are set. Nice!" While thinking like this,
things took another turn.
(It happened again.)
The remaining 30 minutes were spent...
because I was curious.
I wanted to talk with her.
It's either a yes or a no.
(He hasn't talked to one person.)
(Seon Ho allocates 30 minutes to Na Young...)
(and 70 minutes to Jung Ye Ji.)
(He sent 30 minutes to Na Young out of curiosity.)
(Shocked)
Could you prepare some Tylenol for the next episode?
This is incredible.
- Why do you look so angry?
- It's a test of our patience.
This can cause a misunderstanding.
Right.
Based on their conversation,
it seemed like they were both going to spend 100 minutes.
It would've been 200 minutes for them.
They had a conversation that led to 200 minutes.
- They checked each other's hearts.
- Right.
But all of a sudden...
It was a confession.
- Right. It was a confession.
- Right.
Their time was split up again.
Right.
The key figure at this moment...
is Na Young.
Seon Ho hasn't gone on a date with Na Young, right?
- No.
Na Young is here.
It's Na Young.
(Na Young is the last one to enter the Room of Time.)
Today,
I felt a certain change of heart.
"I should do things my way."
"I can't be timid anymore."
I had these thoughts...
and I was determined to go on a date.
(Kim Seon Ho)
I wanted...
to be straightforward.
I might be too honest,
but that's who I am.
(Na Young's time starts heading toward Seon Ho.)
It was strange.
I looked back...
and from the first day until now,
I wasn't able to talk to him properly.
We haven't gone on a single date,
but I kept thinking about him.
Well,
Seon Ho...
he has a cute smile.
He has a nice smile...
and is like a puppy.
And...
he kept showing me his smile.
That made me smile as well.
Being like that...
meant he was on my mind.
"I must have..."
"feelings for him."
(Kim Seon Ho)
"What do you think about me?"
"Am I attractive to you?"
"How do you feel?"
I wanted to find out his heart about these things.
There isn't much time left anyway.
(Na Young allocated 100 minutes to Seon Ho.)
- Gosh, this is bad!
- What?
- This is going to start a fight!
- Hold on! This can't happen!
- Ye Ji can't watch this!
- She can't watch this!
My gosh! Ye Ji can't watch this.
Hold on.
- Things ended up like this?
This is a thriller.
What do we do?
(Feeling dizzy)
Love Against Time must always be double-checked.
Right!
This is incredible.
It happened to be...
- his 30 minutes of curiosity.
- Right.
Who would've imagined those 30 minutes...
to become such a great impact?
Right.
(Nobody expected this outcome.)
Gosh, my head hurts.
(The impact on tomorrow with Na Young's 100 minutes)
(Kim Seon Ho)
With Seon Ho,
I thought,
"I'm sure his heart won't get shaken by someone else."
(The next day)
Well,
I also thought,
"I hope his heart..."
"doesn't get shaken."
I also thought, "What if his heart does get shaken?"
I was worried that...
things could take a turn.
We have spent...
quite some time together.
Just a moment, please.
(Between certainty and looseness,)
(how will they spend their time?)
(Love Against Time)
(Ryun Gi starts to approach Ro Bin.)
(What must I do if I like you?)
(The start of an unexpected change?)
(Can you forget about this date?)
(It was like a movie scene.)
(I have cold feet even in the summer.)
(I need something cold.)
(The moment things felt certain,)
(an unexpected figure gets in between them.)
(Seon Ho was the only one I saw.)
(I will only think about Seon Ho.)
(My heart did race.)
(The start of a twist that will change everything)
(Why won't they come back?)
(What are they doing together?)
(Will his heart get shaken?)
(What are you doing?)
- That can't happen.
- Hey!
(Love Against Time)